Slobodan Komazec, Software Development Engineer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Backend Software Developer with frontend experience and Support Engineer with more than 7 years of software engineering experience in the development of commercial apps. Good knowledge of C#, .NET, ASP.NET MVC. Solid knowledge of frontend technologies such as JavaScript/React, TypeScript HTML, CSS. Has experience in designing databases and queries using MSSQL, MySQL. Able to develop, troubleshoot, debug, and maintain complex applications. Hands-on experience in Agile software lifecycle. Unit testing.

TECHNOLOGY SUMMARY

Languages: C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, VB.NET, HTML, CSS, PowerShell, SQL, KustoQL

Technologies and .NET Framework, ASP.NET, React, Vue, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, DevExpress, NUnit,

Frameworks: Windows Forms, Windows Services, WCF, Microservices

DBMS: MS SQL Server, MySQL, Kusto query

Cloud: Azure, Azure DevOps

IDEs and Tools: Jira, Trello, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, IIS

Other skills: OOP and functional programming, SOLID, MVC, TDD, Agile development, Unit

Testing, Git (GitLab, GitHub), SVN, TFS, Bitbucket, Sitefinity

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Xoran Technologies

Software Development Engineer: January 2018 – Present

Health care, XoranCAT - Software for medical CT scanner

License Server for XoranCAT licensing

<u>Used languages and technologies</u>: C#, VB.NET, ASP.NET MVC, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Azure DevOps, Visual Studio, NUnit.

Microsoft

DevOps Engineer: March 2021 – August 2021

GitHub Platform SRE team

Used languages and technologies: Azure, Azure DevOps, PowerShell, Kusto guery, Git.

Akvelon

Software Development Engineer: November 2020 – February 2021

Application for sending SMS via Twilio – Software for medical CT scanner

Chrome plugin and Outlook VSTO plugin – Better communication between employees and clients

<u>Used languages and technologies</u>: PowerShell, React, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, C#, Docker.

Personal project

Product owner, Developer: July 2019 – June 2020

Dance school management software

<u>Used languages and technologies</u>: Vue.js, Mars server, HTML, CSS.

Lanus

Software Development Engineer: July 2017 – December 2017

Tickets selling website – a website for selling tickets for cultural events.

<u>Used languages and technologies</u>: C#, Angular, Visual Studio, Sitefinity, HTML, CSS.

sTech (Uniqa insurance company)

Software Development Engineer: July 2016 – June 2017

<u>sClaims</u> – Registry of complaints, processing, adjustment, and payment of claims.

<u>Used languages and technologies</u>: C#, Visual Studio, SQL Server, Jira, SVN.

Sampro

Software Development Engineer: September 2015 – June 2016

Textile store management software Warehouse management website Software for barcode readers

Used languages and technologies: C#, SQL Server, ASP.NET MVC, WCF, Visual Studio, SVN.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

University of Belgrade

GIT PROJECTS

React - Code and Text Formatter, Link

React – Marvel Heroes, Link

CONTACT

+381637032905

k.slobodan@yahoo.com